Preliminary Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art archives department records, circa 1890-2007 COR0005.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art archives department records
circa 1890-2007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
COR0005.3.RG
54.25 Linear Feet
The archives department records consists of the archives audiovisual collection, including the photograph collection, some reference vertical files, and some unprocessed files including administrative records of the department itself and folders needing refiling. The records date from approximately 1890 to 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to research with the following exceptions:
Records of the Board of Trustees and records of the Office of the Director are closed to research for 25 years from the date of creation.
Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for the lifetime of the student, and are presumed to be open 75 years after the date of record creation.
Personnel and financial records are closed for 50 years from date of record creation.
Development records are closed to research.
Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Corcoran Institution Board of Trustees donated these records to The George Washington University in 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into eight series: Audiovisual and graphics records, Reference vertical files, Accession and Iron Mountain transfer records, Archivist files, Publications, Exhibition clippings, National Gallery of Art transfer, and Corcoran Library administrative files
Historical narrative
The following history was prepared in 2019 by George Washington University SCRC staff with the support of the Luce Foundation.
The Corcoran Archives was established in January 1980 with the assistance of grants from the National Historical Publications and Records Commission and later the National Endowment for the Humanities, a federal agency. The Corcoran Archives was established with the purpose to collect and preserve the papers which document the heritage of the largest private museum and art school in the nation's capital. The creation of the Corcoran Archives made available to the public for the first time the records of the oldest museum in Washington.
In 2008, due to space reduction, most of the Archives' holdings had to be reboxed and were shipped to offsite storage. However, transfer of materials from the Corcoran's various departments to the archives continued until 2014.
In the spring of 2016 the George Washington University Libraries was selected as the permanent home of the historical archives of the Corcoran Gallery of Art and the Corcoran College of Art + Design.
Scope and Contents
When it was located in the Corcoran, the archives housed two "collections" that are included as series here: The Archival Audiovisual records, and the Reference vertical files. The audiovisual records include a relatively small number of videotapes and slides, but over 1,300 photographs of people, events and buildings related to the Corcoran Gallery and School throughout their histories, which were removed during processing from other record groups. The audiovisual records also contain posters of Corcoran events and exhibits. The record group also contains some unprocessed files including administrative records of the archives itself and folders needing refiling.
- Audiovisual and graphics records, circa 1869-2014; 1950-1984; Series 1; 24 Linear Feet
  Custodial History note
  Audio visual records were transferred to the Archives when the project began in January 1980. They continued to the transferred to the Archives from various departments.
  Scope and Contents
  These records are not particularly strong nor do they well document the entire span of Gallery activities. Many of the Gallery's early photographs were lost, however, some photographs of the building, portraits of Trustees and a few installation shots remain. The collection is more encompassing for the period 1950-1980. Photographs are filed in a self-indexing system which is roughly analogous to the preceding record groups. The slide collection is small, most were taken during the 1970's and consist of installation shots and educational activities. The slides are indexed in the same manner as the photographs.
  Posters from Gallery exhibitions are also included in this group of records. This is not a complete collection of Gallery posters.
  As of 1984, the Gallery had only recently begun to tape and videotape Gallery activities. Future growth in this series was expected. These records include tapes of "At the Corcoran" radio shows where staff members of the Corcoran or Gallery activities were discussed. It is probably not complete.
  Arrangement
  Organized into 4 subseries: Photographs, Slides, Posters and artwork, Audio and video tapes
  - Photographs, circa 1890-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1; 37.5 Linear Feet Over 1,353 images
    Contains black and white photographs, color photographs and negatives of Gallery activities and exhibitions as well as persons associated with the Gallery.
    - CGA I -- Architectural drawings; Annex to CGA, elevation, circa 1880s; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 1)
      Accession Number
      P1983.0166
    - CGA I -- Exterior; Pennsylvania Avenue, line drawing, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 2)
      P1981.0863
    - CGA I -- Exterior; Pennsylvania Avenue, watercolor, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; negative, modern print (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 3)
      P1981.0170
    - CGA I -- Exterior; Engraving from magazine, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; modern print (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 4)
      P2001.0001
    - CGA I -- Exterior; Horse drawn bus with ad for CGA, 1890s?; Series 1 subseries 1; modern print (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 5)
      P1981.0820
    - CGA I -- Exterior; 17th St. and Pennsylvania Ave., circa 1870s; Series 1 subseries 1; 1 negative (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 6)
      P1981.0865
    - CGA I -- Exterior; 17th St. and Pennsylvania Ave., before 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 7)
      P2001.0011
    - CGA I -- Exterior; 17th St. and Pennsylvania Ave., before 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Bell & Bro.) (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 8)
      P2001.0013
    - CGA I -- Exterior; 17th St. and Pennsylvania Ave., before 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 9)
      P2001.0014
    - CGA I -- Exterior; 17th St. and Pennsylvania Ave., before 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; cabinet (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 10)
      P2001.0012
    - CGA I -- Exterior; 17th St. and Pennsylvania Ave., 1972; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 11)
      P1981.0458
    - CGA I -- Exterior; Facade - detail of WWC medallion, 1976; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 12)
      P1981.0864
    - CGA I -- Interior; Main gallery - drawing from New York Daily Graphic, 21 March 1874; Series 1 subseries 1; modern print (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 13)
      P1981.0866
    - CGA I -- Interior; Main picture gallery, circa 1880; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 14)
      P1981.0867B
    - CGA I -- Interior; Picture gallery with other objects [poss. not CGA], circa 1870; Series 1 subseries 1; negative, not P1981.0867a-b view (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 15)
      P1981.0867c
    - CGA I -- Interior; Stereoscopic view of 2nd floor with Greek Slave, circa 1880; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 folders: modern print and negative (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folders 16-17)
      P1981.0913
    - CGA I -- Interior; Students in front of Niagara, circa 1890s; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 folders: mounted print and negative (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folders 18-19)
      P1981.0213
    - CGA I -- Interior; Ground plan, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; modern print (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 20)
      P2001.0008
    - CGA I -- Interior; Plaster cast of Baptistry doors in Florence, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 21)
      P2001.0002
    - CGA I -- Interior; Hall of Bronzes, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 22)
      P2001.0003
    - CGA I -- Interior; Greek Slave in Octagon Room, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 23)
      P2001.0004
    - CGA I -- Interior; Greek Slave, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 24)
      P2001.0010
    - CGA I -- Interior; Vestibule of Hall of Sculpture, Looking West, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 stereoscopes (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 25)
      P2001.0005
    - CGA I -- Interior; The Veiled Nun, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 26)
      P2001.0006
    - CGA I -- Interior; Modern Hall, Showing the Ghiberti Gate, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 27)
      P2001.0007
    - CGA I -- Interior; Picture Gallery (north), right panel, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Box 3, Flat box 1, Folder 28)
      P2001.0009
    - CGA II -- Architectural drawings; 17th St. facade, 1st proposal by Flagg, 1892-1893; Series 1 subseries 1; modern print and negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 1)
      P1983.0053
    - CGA II -- Architectural drawings; 17th St. facade, 2nd proposal by Flagg, 1893; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints and negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 2)
      P1983.0054
    - CGA II -- Architectural drawings; 17th St. facade, 2nd proposal by Flagg, 1893; Series 1 subseries 1; modern print and negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 3)
      P1983.0066
    - CGA II -- Architectural drawings; E Street elevation, 1893; Series 1 subseries 1; modern print, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 4)
      P1981.0869
    - CGA II -- Architectural drawings; Cross section, proposal by Flagg, 1893; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints and negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folders 5-6)
      P1981.0868
    - CGA II -- Architectural drawings; Cross section, proposal by Flagg, details, 1893; Series 1 subseries 1; modern prints of 3 different details (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 7)
      P1981.0251
    - CGA II -- Architectural drawings; 17th St. facade, 1893; Series 1 subseries 1; 12 prints (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 8)
      P1981.0871A
    - CGA II -- Architectural drawings; New York Avenue elevation, 1893; Series 1 subseries 1; modern print and negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 9)
      P1981.0108
    - CGA II -- Architectural drawings; Models of galleries for Halpert collection, circa 1960s; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, different views (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 10)
      P1983.0265
    - CGA II -- Architectural drawings; Proposed New York Avenue addition, 1970; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints, different views (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 11)
      P1984.0005
    - CGA II -- Construction; June 26, 1893 [groundbreaking], Series 1 subseries 1; modern print and negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 12)
      P1983.0055
    - CGA II -- Construction; July 22, 1893 [clearing ground], Series 1 subseries 1; modern print and negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 13)
      P1983.0056
    - CGA II -- Construction; May 10, 1894 [preparations for cornerstone], Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 14)
      P1983.0067
    - CGA II -- Construction; May 10, 1894 [preparations for cornerstone], Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 15)
      P1983.0068
    - CGA II -- Construction; May 10, 1894 [laying the cornerstone], Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 16)
      P1981.0883
    - CGA II -- Construction; May 10, 1894 [laying the cornerstone], Series 1 subseries 1; modern print (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 17)
      P1981.0229
    - CGA II -- Construction; May 10, 1894 [address at cornerstone laying], Series 1 subseries 1; modern print (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 18)
      P2001.0015
    - CGA II -- Construction; June 14, 1894, Series 1 subseries 1; 3 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 19)
      P1983.0070
    - CGA II -- Construction; June 18, 1894, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 20)
      P1983.0069
    - CGA II -- Construction; June 22, 1894, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 21)
      P1983.0059
    - CGA II -- Construction; June 22, 1894, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 22)
      P1983.0071
    - CGA II -- Construction; July 12, 1894, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 23)
      P1983.0060
    - CGA II -- Construction; July 12, 1894, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 24)
      P1983.0072
    - CGA II -- Construction; July 26, 1894, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 25)
      P1983.0061
    - CGA II -- Construction; March 6, 1895, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 26)
      P1983.0073
    - CGA II -- Construction; March 6, 1895, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 27)
      P1983.0074
    - CGA II -- Construction; March 6, 1895, Series 1 subseries 1; 3 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 28)
      P1983.0062
    - CGA II -- Construction; April 25, 1895, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 29)
      P1983.0063
    - CGA II -- Construction; April 25, 1895, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 30)
      P1983.0075
    - CGA II -- Construction; May 1, 1895, Series 1 subseries 1; modern print, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 31)
      P1983.0064
    - CGA II -- Construction; May 1, 1895, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 32)
      P1983.0065
    - CGA II -- Construction; May 1, 1895, Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 33)
      P1983.0076
    - CGA II -- Construction; Near completion, 1896-1897; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 34)
      P1983.0077
    - CGA II -- Construction; Near completion, 1896-1897; Series 1 subseries 1; mounted print, identical to P1981.0084 (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 35)
      P1981.0230
    - CGA II -- Construction; Near completion, 1896-1897; Series 1 subseries 1; mounted print, identical to P1981.0230 (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 36)
      P1981.0884
    - CGA II -- Construction; Roof and skylight work of Wolfsteiner Co., 1924; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 37)
      P1983.0093
    - CGA II -- Construction; Roof and skylight work of Wolfsteiner Co., 1924; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 38)
      P1983.0093A
    - CGA II -- Construction; Roof and skylight work of Wolfsteiner Co., 1924; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 39)
      P1983.0093B
    - CGA II -- Construction; Roof and skylight work of Wolfsteiner Co., 1924; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 40)
      P1983.0093D
    - CGA II -- Construction; Roof and skylight work of Wolfsteiner Co., 1924; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 41)
      P1983.0093E
    - CGA II -- Construction; Roof and skylight work of Wolfsteiner Co., 1924; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 42)
      P1983.0093F
    - CGA II -- Construction; Roof and skylight work of Wolfsteiner Co., 1924; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 43)
      P1983.0093G
    - CGA II -- Construction; Roof and skylight work of Wolfsteiner Co., 1924; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 44)
      P1983.0093H
    - CGA II -- Construction; Brick chimney damage, 1975; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 45)
      P1984.0044
    - CGA II -- Construction; Air-conditioning system, 1974-1977; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 contact sheets (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 46)
      P1984.0047
    - CGA II -- Construction; Roof repairs, 1977; Series 1 subseries 1; 12 prints (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 47)
      P1984.0045
    - CGA II -- Construction; Admiral Snead giving tour of climate control sys., 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, negatives (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 48)
      P1983.0023
    - CGA II -- Construction; Air-conditioning installation, 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, negatives (Box 3, Flat box 2, Folder 49)
      P1983.0017
    - CGA II -- Exerior; Dedication plaque, 1897; Series 1 subseries 1; mounted print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 1)
      P1981.0217
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. with horse-drawn carriages, circa 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints, 1 negative (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 2)
      P1981.0233
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., circa 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 modern prints, 2 negatives (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folders 3-4)
      P1981.0885
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., circa 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; print, negative (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 5)
      P1981.0231
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. with new plantings, circa 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; a-c 3 prints each (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folders 6-9)
      P1981.0232A-C
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. with new plantings, circa 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 10)
      P1981.0887A
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. with new plantings, circa 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 11)
      P1981.0887B
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicycle, circa 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; stereoscope (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 12)
      P1981.0001
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicycle, circa 1900; Series 1 subseries 1; mounted print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 13)
      P1984.0241
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicycle postcard, circa 1910-1920s; Series 1 subseries 1; 7 postcards (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 14)
      P1981.0873
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicycle, circa 1915; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 15)
      P1981.0886
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., Mrs. Cavalli with lions, 1927; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 16)
      P1983.0001
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., 1920s; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 17)
      P1983.0052
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., 1936; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 18)
      P1983.0126
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicycle, circa 1930s; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 19)
      P2001.0021
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., 1940s; Series 1 subseries 1; a 3 prints, b 2 negs (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folders 20-21)
      P1981.0237A-B
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th Street, circa 1940; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 22)
      P1981.0234
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., 1940s?; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 23)
      P1981.0238
    - CGA II -- Exterior; South corner of 17th St. facade, 1940s; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 24)
      P1981.0882
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicycle, 1949; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 modern prints, negative (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folders 25-26)
      P1981.0876B
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. entrance, Lugin show sign, 1954; Series 1 subseries 1; a 3 negatives, b 1 print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folders 27-28)
      P1981.0880A-B
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. entrance, 1955; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 29)
      P1981.0243
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. entrance, door knocker, 1966; Series 1 subseries 1; negative, print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 30)
      P1981.0889
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. facade, upper north corner, 1960s; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 31)
      P1981.0242
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. facade, upper north corner, 1960s; Series 1 subseries 1; negatives (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 32)
      P1981.0879
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. facade, 1960s; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 color transparencies (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 33)
      P1981.0241
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicycle: sculpture on corner, 1960s; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 34)
      P1981.0239
    - CGA II -- Exterior; E St., 1962; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 35)
      P1981.0878
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Building deterioration for Mellon grant, 1970s; Series 1 subseries 1; 8 prints (5 views) (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folders 36-37)
      P1983.0160A-B
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Aerial views, 1974-1977; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 contact sheets (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 38)
      P1984.0049
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., Gene Davis banner, 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 39)
      P1982.0012
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. entrance, 1970s; Series 1 subseries 1; color print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 40)
      P1982.0008
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. entrance, 1976; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 41)
      P1981.0236
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. entrance, "Dedicated to Art", 1970s; Series 1 subseries 1; negatives (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 42)
      P1981.0244
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. entrance, 36th Biennial, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints, different views (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 43)
      P1982.0011
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St. and other views, 1970s; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 negatives, different views (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 44)
      P1981.0875
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., Mimi Herbert banner, 1976; Series 1 subseries 1; a & b one print each (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folders 45-46)
      P1982.0013A-B
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., Mimi Herbert banner, 1976; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 47)
      P1981.0235
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicycle, aerial views, 1970s; Series 1 subseries 1; print, contact sheets, negatives (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folders 48-49)
      P1981.0874A-B
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicycle, aerial views, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 50)
      P1981.0669
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Griffin, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 51)
      P1981.0457
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St, collapsed wall, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints, different views (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 52)
      P1981.0727
    - CGA II -- Exterior; 17th St., Hammer collection banners, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; a 2 contact sheets; b 5 prints, different views (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folders 53-54)
      P1981.080A-B
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicycle, from FDIC building, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; a contact sheets, b negatives (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folders 55-56)
      P1981.0067A-B
    - CGA II -- Exterior; Hemicyle, from above [FDIC building], undated; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 3, Flat box 3, Folder 57)
      P1981.0876A
    - CGA II -- Maps and floor plans; Street map, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 3, Flat box 4, Folder 1)
      P1981.0211
    - CGA II -- Maps and floor plans; 1st floor, before 1928; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 4, Folder 2)
      P2001.0020
    - CGA II -- Maps and floor plans; Floor plans, various views/floors, after 1928; Series 1 subseries 1; negatives (Box 3, Flat box 4, Folders 3-6)
      P1981.0872A-d
    - CGA II -- Interior; Atrium, sketch of gallery opening, 1897; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 3, Flat box 4, Folder 7)
      P1981.0246